Oliver Wolcott, Jr. Papers
Connecticut Historical Society
- II. Correspondence
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; portrait of Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1796; (10 items) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Letters and copies of letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; letter to Eliza Wolcott; An Act Authorizing a detachment from the Militia of the United States; copy of the Last Will and Testament of Oliver Wolcott (1794)., 1797; (19 items) (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Letters and copies of letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; letter to Eliza Wolcott., 1798; (17 items) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Letters and copies of letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1799; (19 items) (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Letters with related material to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1800; (8 items) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1801 - 1802; (5 items) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Letters with related material to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1803; (18 items) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - February, 1803; (18 items) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1804; (20 items) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1804; (23 items) (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May, 1804; (14 items) (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1804; (8 items) (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July, 1804; (14 items) (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August - September, 1804; (21 items) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October - November, 1804; (22 items) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1804; (15 items) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January, 1805; (17 items) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February, 1805; (15 items) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1805; (22 items) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1805; (13 items) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May, 1805; (20 items) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1805; (14 items) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July, 1805; (23 items) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August, 1805; (19 items) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September, 1805; (20 items) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October, 1805; (10 items) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and Charles Higbee., November, 1805; (8 items) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1805; (15 items) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - March, 1806; (11 items) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April - May, 1806; (13 items) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June - July, 1806; (10 items) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August - September, 1806; (15 items) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October, 1806; (14 items) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1806; (19 items) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1806; (16 items) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January 1 - 15, 1807; (7 items) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January 15 - 31, 1807; (21 items) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and Jarvis Mudge., February, 1807; (18 items) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1807; (15 items) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April 1 - 15, 1807; (15 items) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April 16 - 30, 1807; (14 items) (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May, 1807; (17 items) (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1807; (19 items) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July, 1807; (14 items) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August, 1807; (19 items) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September, 1807; (17 items) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October, 1807; (10 items) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1807; (14 items) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1807; (18 items) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and Henry Wylie and Co., December 1 - 15, 1807; (20 items) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December 16 - 31, 1807; (6 items) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January, 1808; (15 items) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February 1 - 15, 1808; (17 items) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February 16 - 29, 1808; (12 items) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1808; (13 items) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1808; (16 items) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. One letter to David Humphreys., May, 1808; (25 items) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1808; (10 items) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July 1808; (5 items) (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. One letter to Theodore Dwight., August - September, 1808; (8 items) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October - November, 1808; (13 items) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1808; (7 items) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - January - February, 1809, (14 items) (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March - April, 1809; (9 items) (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott Jr., May - June, 1809; (13 items) (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - August, 1809; (9 items) (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September, 1809; (10 items) (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. (One in French), October, 1809; (2 items) (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1809; (16 items) (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December 1 - 15, 1809; (23 items) (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December 16 - 31, 1809; (12 items) (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr.; letter to Willing and Francis., January 1 - 15, 1810; (26 items) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January 16 - 31, 1810; (12 items) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February, 1810; (21 items) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1810; (25 items) (Box 35)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1810; (22 items) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May 1 - 15, 1810; (13 items) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May 16 - 31, 1810; (10 items) (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. One letter to Richmond and Andrews., June 1 - 15, 1810; (15 items) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June 16 - 30, 1810; (20 items) (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July 1 - 15, 1810; (14 items) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July 16 - 31, 1810; (16 items) (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August, 1810; (22 items) (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September, 1810; (12 items) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October, 1810; (19 items) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1810; (16 items) (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1810; (19 items) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1810; (16 items) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January, 1811; (19 items) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February, 1811; (18 items) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. One letter to Samuel M. Hopkins., March, 1811; (23 items) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1811; (20 items) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May, 1811; (12 items) (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1811; (14 items) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July, 1811; (23 items) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August, 1811; (14 items) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September, 1811; (17 items) (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October, 1811; (20 items) (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., Nov. 1 - 15, 1811; (17 items) (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., Nov. 16 - 30, 1811; (18 items) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1811; (22 items) (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January, 1812; (19 items) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February, 1812; (21 items) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1812; (22 items) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1812; (13 items) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. One letter to Frederick Wolcott., May, 1812; (12 items) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1812; (15 items) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July, 1812; (11 items) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., August, 1812; (10 items) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September, 1812; (11 items) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., October, 1812; (6 items) (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., November, 1812; (14 items) (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., December, 1812; (6 items) (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January, 1813; (7 items) (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., February, 1813; (8 items) (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., March, 1813; (9 items) (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., April, 1813; (12 items) (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May, 1813; (13 items) (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., June, 1813; (16 items) (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - December, 1813; (8 items) (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - June, 1814; (15 items) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - August, 1814; (17 items) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., September - October, 1814; (17 items) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. Letter to James T. Watson., November - December, 1814; (12 items) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - June, 1815; (17 items) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., July - December, 1815; (6 items) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr. One letter to Brigadier General Levi Lusk., 1816; (8 items) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Draft of letter from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May 9, 1817; (1 item) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1818; (3 items) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1819; (4 items) (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1820; (3 items) (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1822; (4 items) (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1823; (7 items) (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1824; (6 items) (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1825; (22 items) (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1825; (24 items) (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., January - April, 1826; (15 items) (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., May - December, 1826; (16 items) (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1827; (10 items) (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., including letters to and from his son John S. Wolcott., 1828; (8 items) (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Letters to Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1829; (5 items) (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Wolcott family letters., 1790 - 1864; (10 items) (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Letter book, Oliver Wolcott, Jr.'s reports and letters., 1789 - 1803; (1 item) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Letter book., 1791 - 1794; (1 item) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Letter book. Copies of letters to and from Oliver Wolcott, Jr. and Tench Coxe., 1797; (1 item) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Copies of letters from Oliver Wolcott, Jr., 1793 - 1799; (18 items) (Box 39, Folder 4)
- III. United States Government appointments
  - Silas Deane's Accounts with the United States with the remarks of Thomas Barclay. Copy of the originals in the Office of the Secretary of State. Auditor's Office., 1776 - 1784; (1 item) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - A List of Accounts settled by the present Treasury Department and entered on Record in the Register's Office, upon which Balances were stated due to the U. States, in relation to Transactions of the late Government, and which remain unpaid., 1792 - 1794; (1 items) (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Expenses of carrying into effect US Valuation Act in Connecticut, 1799; (1 items) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Statements of the Certified Debt of the United States., 1795 - 1800; (2 items) (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - A General View of the Finances of Great Britain., 1799; (1 item) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Balances; An Account of all Sums which have been Transferred from the Books of the Treasury to the Books of the Accountant of the War Department., 1801; (2 items) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Balances due on Personal Accounts in the Books of Receipts and Expenditures of the United States on the 31 December 1800., (1 items) (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Receipts, Expenditures, Public Debt... United States, prepared by Richard Rogers., 1806; (1 items) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Circular letters and commissions concerning land valuation in Connecticut., 1798; (10 items) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Circular letters and commissions and concerning land valuation in Connecticut., 1798; (19 items) (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut land valuation records., 1798 - 1799; (20 items) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (A - B)., 1791 - 1792; (29 items) (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (C - G), 1791 - 1792; (30 items) (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (H - K), 1791 - 1792; (27 items) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (L)., 1791 - 1792; (18 items) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (M)., 1791 - 1792; (21 items) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (N - P), 1791 - 1792; (13 items) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (S), 1791 - 1792; (41 items) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Members of the Second Congress (T - Z), 1791 - 1792; (32 items) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Receipts for Debentures by Auxiliary Staff to Second Congress, 1791 - 1792; (16 items) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Letters and related material from the Treasury Department concerning shipping., 1793; (11 items) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., 1792 - 1794; (14 items) (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., January, 1795; ( items) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., February, 1795; (12 items) (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., March, 1795; (17 items) (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., April, 1795; (14 items) (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., May, 1795; (13 items) (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., June, 1795; (16 items) (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., July, 1795; (12 items) (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., August, 1795; (18 items) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., September, 1795; (13 items) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., October, 1795; (13 items) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., November, 1795; (15 items) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., December, 1795; (17 items) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash; Wolcott's document dividers., 1795; (2 items) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., January, 1796; (12 items) (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., February, 1796; (15 items) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., March, 1796; (12 items) (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., April, 1796; (12 items) (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., May, 1796; (15 items) (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., June, 1796; (13 items) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., July, 1796; (12 items) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., August, 1796; (14 items) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., September, 1796; (12 items) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., October, 1796; (15 items) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., November, 1796; (12 items) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., December, 1796; (12 items) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., 1796; (16 items) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., 1797; (16 items) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., January, 1797; (13 items) (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., February, 1797; (11 items) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., March, 1797; (12 items) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., April, 1797; (12 items) (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash, Wolcott's document dividers., 1796 - 1797; (3 items) (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., May, 1797; (14 items) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., July, 1797; (10 items) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., July, 1797; (10 items) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., August, 1797; (7 items) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., September, 1797; (4 items) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., October, 1797; (5 items) (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., November, 1797; (7 items) (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., December, 1797; (8 items) (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., 1798; (18 items) (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., 1799; (14 items) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., January, 1798; (10 items) (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., February, 1798; (8 items) (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., March, 1798; (8 items) (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., April, 1798; (10 items) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., May, 1798; (7 items) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., June, 1798; (7 items) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., July, 1798; (8 items) (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., August, 1798; (7 items) (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., September, 1798; (8 items) (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., October, 1798; (8 items) (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., November, 1798; (5 items) (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., December, 1798; (10 items) (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., January, 1799; (8 items) (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., February, 1799; (8 items) (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., March, 1799; (8 items) (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., April, 1799; (11 items) (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., May, 1799; (8 items) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., June, 1799; (8 items) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., July, 1799; (10 items) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., August, 1799; (6 items) (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., September, 1799; (9 items) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., October, 1799; (7 items) (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., November, 1799; (6 items) (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., December, 1799; (7 items) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., January, 1800; (8 items) (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., February, 1800; (8 items) (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., March, 1800; (10 items) (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., April, 1800; (12 items) (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., May, 1800; (9 items) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly returns of cash., June, 1800; (6 items) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., June, 1800; (3 items) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., August, 1800; (11 items) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., September, 1800; (7 items) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., October, 1800; (9 items) (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., November, 1800; (10 items) (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - U. S. Treasury Department. Weekly state of balances., December, 1800; (11 items) (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - A Statement of the Trade of Great Britain with all parts of the World during the period of two Years., 1791 - 1793; (1 items) (Box 47, Folder 9)